DEVENYE DUNN

BLOCKCHAIN ENGINEER

devenyedunn934@gmail.com 5615 Sandial Dr. +1 (202) 854devenye.github.io/person linkedin.com/in/devenye934 8584 Jacksonville, FL, US

SUMMARY

Highly skilled blockchain engineer with rich practical experience in creating smart contracts, NFTs, and web3 projects. I have tackled numerous projects and intricate business challenges across different facets of blockchain. My expertise has played a pivotal role in the success of companies like Microsoft (Solana), Jungle Cat, Honey Finance, and more. A creative and enthusiastic self-learner with a wealth of experience in blockchain development.

EXPERIENCE

Microsoft | New York, US

September 2023 - February 2024 Blockchain Lead Engineer

- - traceability and reducing counterfeit incidents, which directly contributed to the growth in client trust and business volume. • Led a team of developers in the successful migration of a traditional loyalty points system to a new blockchain platform, doubling

Engineered a proprietary blockchain solution for a supply chain management system of \$MSFT(MICROSOFT COIN), increasing

- redemption rates and increasing partner participation.
- Implemented smart contract audit processes that improved code quality and security, leading to a 50% decrease in vulnerabilities detected and a 100% success rate in passing third-party security audits.

Jungle Cat | Arizona, US

June 2023 - July 2023

Senior Blockchain Engineer

- Designed and developed Jungle Cat NFT, a component of the new blockchain ecosystem for the business.
- Developed and deployed high-quality, quick, and secure smart contracts that integrate Jungle Cat NFT on the Solana Blockchain System.
- Increased team productivity and effectiveness by conducting in-depth code reviews and giving junior developers technical direction on best practices for blockchain development.

Honey Finance | Los Angeles CA, US

December 2022 - June 2023

Full Stack Blockchain Developer

- Developed Smart Contracts working on Hivemapper Network based on Solana Blockchain System, which directly contributed to a 30% growth in security.
- Contributed to the design and architecture of decentralized applications (dApps) utilizing blockchain technology.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and implement end-to-end blockchain solutions for various industries.
- Created RESTful APIs for seamless integration of blockchain applications with front-end interfaces.
- Developed Front-end side that users can send NFT buying, selling and exchanging request to blockchain system, using Web3.js, Next.js, with user-friendly attitude.

Ratio Finance | San Francisco CA, US

September 2022 - December 2022

Senior Blockchain Developer

- Researched, installed, and debugged an smart contract system reducing transaction times and failures.
- Designed and implemented smart contracts using Rust on the Solana blockchain to automate key processes for a supply chain management company, reducing operational costs by 15%.
- Built a front-end application for buying and exchanging NFTs using React and Web3.js.

Molana Pte, Ltd | Novena, Singapore

July 2022 - September 2022

Junior Blockchain Developer

- Worked collaboratively with cross-functional teams to integrate new technology of the company into existing systems.
- Developed Smart Contracts integrating Molana into blockchain ecosystem for swaping with other cryptocurrencies.
- Contributed to the popularity of Molana cryptocurrency over people, improved crypto's secure, system speed and business.

Hawksight | Singapore, Singapore

September 2021 - June 2022

Junior Blockchain Developer

- Collaborated with the team to draw up a new system design that improved blockchain scalability.
- Developed and implemented smart contracts using Rust on the Solana blockchain platform.

EDUCATION

Jacksonville University | Jacksonville, FL, US

May 2016 - May 2020 Computer Science

SKILLS

- Blockchain Core Development Smart Contract Engineering with Rust, Solana
- Rust + Anchor + React/Next + Typescript
- Cryptography, Security Audit, Tokenomics
- Cosmos, Golang, Layer2

- DeFi Swap, Staking, Bond, Farm, Vesting
- DEX Perpetuals, Leverage, Limit Order Book Lending, Liquid Staking, Voting, Launchpad
- NFT Staking, pNFT, Candy Machine, cNFT
- Gaming, Oracle, Stablecoin, DAO